I will now proceed to break the curse.
I didn't think you'd make it in time.
Analyzing the curse?
Of course I'd make it in time.
You'd be left beyond help otherwise.
Hurry up and go to sleep already.
I can't have you conscious for the procedure.
Half a year, huh?
It passed by in a flash.
You're still awake!
I can't fall asleep that quickly.
When I first saw you, I thought
you were a woman made for me.
I had no idea why this curse was cast on me,
but I believed it was so I'd meet you.
Yes.
I came here to meet you.
Tinasha.
What is it?
You're really going to break it?
Yes.
Please do.
~ Returning the Promise ~
It's hard to believe that
Lady Tinasha's returned home.
To think we're here for her coronation today.
She'll be inheriting the spirits
of Tuldarr as well.
Showing off the spirits after all this time...
Could there be an ulterior motive?
Don't worry.
She may be inheriting them,
but I doubt she can handle more than one.
She already has a spirit serving her...
Appear before me...
spirits that rest in Tuldarr by ancient pact.
I am Tinasha As Meyer Ur Aeterna Tuldarr.
As your ruler, my declaration defines you.
Come to me.
Look at that!
That can't be!
All twelve spirits?!
Heed my command, twelve spirits of Tuldarr.
As your ruler, I declare an end
to our ancient, long-lived pact.
You are hereby released
from your binding chains.
This means you are now free.
Lilia
You may do as you wish.
Wh-What?!
Bygone is the era in which a ruler
must wield fearsome power.
Tuldarr is a powerful nation,
even without the spirits.
Legis, did you know she would do this?!
Yes, Father.
How absurd!
For the next year, I will be the last queen
to succeed our ancient traditions.
Prince Legis will take the throne after me
and rule Tuldarr with
a new government in place.
There you have it.
Thanks for everything you've done for us.
Karr
We can really do whatever we want?
Of course.
Then I'll take this chance to serve you
as a spirit until you die, little girl.
I'm still free to consider you my queen.
Lady Tinasha, I'll stay with you as well!
Huh? Maybe I should stay, too.
Nil
I know I won't be bored
with Her Majesty around.
Feel free to leave, Nil!
You're in the way!
They're quite fond of you.
I'd say it's more like
they enjoy messing with me.
Itz
I thank you for declaring an end to our pact.
But, as Karr suggests, please allow us
to stay with you until the end.
We choose to obey you of our own free will.
Well, I did say you could do as you wish.
Please stay with me for the time being, then.
It would be our pleasure.
I don't think anyone expected her to do that.
I suppose even with Queen Tinasha's bloodline,
there would still have come a time
when the spirits could no longer be inherited.
That said, as long as the spirits
remain while she's in power,
that's enough to deter foreign intervention.
The question is whether they can establish
a new government in that time.
Where's Tinasha?
She's fighting with my father.
I imagine it won't be much longer.
King Oscar. Do you have a moment?
There she is.
Y-You again?!
What do you mean, "again?"
Never mind.
There should be a barrier up.
I easily managed my way in.
How insecure.
Not many people can break my barrier.
That was quite a bold move back there.
Well, I'd made my decision a while back.
What will you do after you step down?
I think it'd be best if I married Legis.
I'm sure Calste would be relieved as well.
Why don't you come with me instead?
What?
In other words, be my wife.
I don't think it's a bad deal.
With a new government, it'd be safer
to form an alliance with another nation.
Some may see you as a danger,
but they wouldn't dare to take on
both Tuldarr and Farsas.
M-Maybe you're right, but hold on!
No, that was cowardly of me.
Let me start over.
I want you.
That's why I want your hand in marriage.
Nothing more.
Well, you still have a year left.
Take some time to think about it.
W-Wait a minute!
Why the window?!
Wait, no!
I thought you weren't interested in me!
My kingdom comes before my personal emotions.
That is why I tried my best
not to grow attached to you.
But that all changes if you're
going to abdicate the throne.
I want you by my side.
I don't want anyone else to have you.
If you want me, I'm yours.
Until next time.
She is Tuldarr's greatest treasure.
Will you offer us what she's worth?
If that's what she wants, then sure.
What is it like in the future you've seen?
Did she end up marrying me?
Lady Tinasha.
You need to train to separate
your emotions from your magic.
I did... a long time ago.
It didn't stick.
Yes...
Next time, I'll use a steel cup.
Why not deal with the source?
Like eliminating him.
Not happening!
I don't know why you're hesitating.
You came here to meet him
in the first place, right?
That's true...
But this isn't what things were like before.
You'll come and find me for sure.
You'll find happiness.
It was the old him that said that.
Still, he realized why I came here.
And told me not to feel sorry...
I was really happy to hear that.
I was glad I came to this era.
But marrying him?
What's wrong with that?
I'm not sure why he chose me.
Not to mention, he doesn't know
what it was like back in the Dark Age.
That's true.
Back then, betraying others
was practically a part of growing up.
Was it that bad?!
I mean, I guess it was...
So perhaps Akashia's wielder actually
plans on betraying you as well.
You mean to take me as a hostage for Tuldarr?
That'd be nice and easy to understand.
So should I eliminate him?
I said "no!"
I'm glad you seem to be enjoying yourself.
When you suggested traveling through time,
I thought you'd finally lost your mind.
That's how little faith you had in me?!
Lilia, how do you think he was able
to travel back in time?
It defies the laws of magic.
I couldn't say.
Maybe it just looks like he traveled back
in time, and it's something else entirely.
It's human folly to try
and understand everything.
Even our kind cannot
perceive many other realms.
That's why strange phenomena with
no explanation occur from time to time.
There were some weird happenings
during my previous reign.
Like the Harvesting.
Oh, those mysterious ruins.
You should get some sunlight
now and then for your health.
I don't like the sun.
I heard the witch took the throne.
It'll be fine.
What about Farsas?
Akashia is the one uncertain factor,
but it doesn't matter.
We can split the two up and take on the witch.
She's the weaker one.
Really?
Mentally, that is.
And that's the important part.
When the world is altered,
it converges back near its original state,
but it can't fully revert back.
So the world is waiting for an opportunity.
One push to bring it back
to its original state.
I don't want you to die.
It'll be fine.
The ruins unearthed in the southwest?
Didn't we send out an expedition?
None of them have returned?
All the residents of the villages
near the ruins have gone missing, too.
Also, the entrance to the ruins are enchanted
with a spell to prevent deterioration,
but its composition uses techniques
unseen in known magical history.
Therefore, I believe we should seal off the ruins.
Just as you hoped for...
Or perhaps feared?
I'll go check it out.
Outsider Ruins    Southwestern Farsas
If anything happens,
feel free to retreat.
Make safety your first priority.
Yes!
It's too pristine.
The walls are seamless.
We're pretty deep inside now.
Yes.
You'd expect to pass through the mountain
and reach the surface by now.
Your Majesty!
General Granfort has gone missing!
What?
I can't find the other soldiers, either!
We already have people missing?
I didn't sense anything out of the ordinary.
What's going on here?
Step back!
Your Majesty!
That's not good.
We're all split up now.
What?
What in the world?
Are these ruins full of ghosts?
Are you... Tinasha?
Thanks, Nark!
How sickening.
This will give me nightmares.
Oscar?!
Oscar, wait!
It sure is a good resemblance.
Wait! Y-You're too close!
The more I look, the more you resemble her.
It's the real me!
W-Wait, I'm really...
So? How'd you come here?
You knew all along?!
Of course I did.
Just a bit of banter.
A magical attack made contact
with the barrier I placed on you,
so I went to Farsas to see what happened.
Als told me everything, so I came here.
So that was it.
Did you fight a mage?
Yeah.
You, but slightly younger.
Huh?
So it got a record of me after all?
A record?
This place is sort of a repository
to preserve records of humans.
I don't understand the mechanics, but it
captures humans to create copies of them.
The copies it creates
are stored as simple data,
but they can also materialize
to get rid of any detected intruders.
So that's what I faced.
Tuldarr records refer to it as the Harvesting.
I came here four hundred years ago,
and I found myself captured.
I managed to escape halfway through,
but I guess it got enough data
to materialize me.
That's an ominous name.
What happens to those it captures?
Duplication chambers.
They should be sleeping here.
I'll open a teleportation
portal at the entrance,
so go wake the people inside.
They're encased in cocoons,
but it's safe to cut them free.
A large number of guardians will spawn,
but I'll take care of them.
Will you be okay on your own?
I'll be fine.
But I might not be able to last long,
so please hurry.
Call me if things look bad.
Don't get hurt.
I'll keep that in mind.
Go on.
Yeah.
Steel unformed into blade,
defined by my words.
Rift of negation.
Time unbound to pain.
Reject them.
Doan. Wake up!
There's a teleportation portal at the entrance.
Destroy the cocoons
and evacuate the people inside.
If you find palace soldiers, have them help!
At your command...
Karr! Senn!
Yeah, yeah.
You called?
This place again?
I hate it here.
Senn
Stop complaining and get to work, Karr.
Can you keep going a little longer?
I'm fine. I can do it.
Tinasha!
The enemy's begun to interfere.
They're trying to close the portal by force.
What?
For crying out loud...
There's no end to them.
Tinasha, lend me your vision.
What?
Please be careful.
I'll be fine.
Oh.
He's pretty good!
This is it.
The core...
Why are you laughing?
You're making a funny face.
Is now the time?!
Damn you, insider...
What was that?
Was I hearing things?
What in the world created those ruins?
I'd like to know, but I don't have
the slightest clue.
It operates on forces
outside the laws of magic,
so there's nothing to go off of.
Even on other planes of existence,
there are no laws that defy the laws of magic.
That would mean going against this very world.
What about outside this world?
What? Outside this world?
There's no way to prove that even exists.
It's impossible.
You have plenty of time
to answer my engagement offer.
We still have a year left.
Have you received any other
proposals since then?
From seven countries or so.
Oh?
Don't give me that look!
They're proposing just because
they want a magical weapon!
Are you sure?
What do you even see in me?
You're weird.
What does that mean?
You don't know anything about me.
In the Dark Age, they used
to call me the Ice Queen...
You'd regret spending
your life with me if you knew.
Really?
If you want to tell me, then tell me.
If you want to hide it, then hide it.
I could know everything,
and I'd still feel the same.
I did my best to make sure
you'd expect nothing from me.
You're fine if you end up regretting it?
Yeah.
I want to spend my life with you.
Let me indulge my personal
emotions for once in my life.
I understand what you're
trying to say very well.
I'd rather not keep you waiting,
so here's my answer.
Thank you for the kind offer.
If you'll have me, I'll gladly accept.
You're too close.
Get used to it.
~ Bloodless Scars ~